威尔 · 森塔斯: 我不想让任何人对这种差异感到困惑。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I don't want anyone
confused by this difference here.
所以我们必须声明 outer，运行 outer，然后把 incrementCounter 输入到 myNewFunction,
So we had declare outer, run outer, out
came incrementCounter into myNewFunction,
运行 myNewFunction，再次运行 myNewFunction，好吗？
run myNewFunction,
run myNewFunction again, okay?
我们现在知道这一点了。
We know this bit now.
我的新功能，当它出来的时候，带着所有的背包数据,
myNewFunction, when it came out,
got with it all that backpacked data,
当它跑出来的时候，得到了所有的背包数据。
when it came out of running outer,
got all that backpacked data.
也就是说，我们运行了 myNewFunction，我们可以访问背包里的所有数据。
Meaning, we ran myNewFunction, we had
access to all that data in the backpack.
从增量计数器作为一个函数在运行中诞生开始
From when increment counter was born
as a function inside the running of
在我的新函数中加入增量计数。
outer out came increment
count into my new function.
现在有了增量计数器，但是,
myNewFunction has now
increment counter but also,
通过它的隐藏范围属性，所有周围的实时数据时，它是
through its hidden scope property all
the surrounding live data from when it was
我们运行新功能的时候，我也是这样出生的。
born as well me when we
run my new function.
我们仍然可以使用 myNewFunctions 背包
We still have access to
myNewFunctions backpack
增量计数器，周围的实时数据。
increment counters, surrounding live data.
如果你看看这里的代码,
If you look at this code here,
这是我们的外部你看，我把增量计数器现在对，多行。
there's our outer you see I put increment
counter now on to, multiple lines.
然后我们来到这里，这都是一样的,
Then we've got over here,
this is all the same,
右外部 myNewFunction 是外部函数的返回。
right outer myNewFunction
is a return of outer.
这是增量计数面试一切到这里完全一样。
Which was increment count interview
everything up to here exactly the same.
事情发生了变化。
Where things change.
我现在在这里添加了一个新的代码块。
I've now added a new block of code here.
不要因为我把它绕了一圈而感到困惑
Don't get confused by the fact
I kind of looped it around but
线程的执行是[声音]和下来，右，两列基本上。
the thread of execution is going [SOUND]
and down, right, two columns basically.
这里没有什么深奥的东西。
There's nothing profound here.
我不能把所有的东西放在一张幻灯片上。
I cannot fit all on one slide.
这是一个新的代码块，有三行代码。
And so, here we got this new block
with three lines of code here.
又一轮的外在,
Another running of outer,
另一个新的执行上下文，我们将其输出分类为另一个函数。
another new execution context, the output
of which we sort into another function.
然后再运行另一个函数两次。
We're then gonna run
another function twice.
让我们从最后三行开始，丹,
Let's do it down to
the last three lines Dan,
我们在左手边讨论什么功能？
where we speak on the left hand
side here about what function?
阿丹: 我们正在宣布。
&gt;&gt; Dan: We're declaring it.
所以在所有的函数中，常量的作用是已经完成的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So in all function will
function what constants already done.
阿丹: 我们在声明一个常量，另一个函数。
&gt;&gt; Dan: We're declaring
a constant another function.
威尔 · 森特斯: 太好了，谢谢你，丹。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Perfect, thank you, Dan.
我不会再道歉了。
I will not apologize one more time.
但我为我的道歉感到抱歉。
But I am sorry for the apologies.
好的，另一个函数。
All right, another function.
很好，我们现在要运行的另一个函数是什么，丹？
Good, another function we're now
gonna have to go and run what Dan?
丹: 外面。
&gt;&gt; Dan: Outer.
威尔 · 森特斯: 外部，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Outer, exactly.
那么现在另一个函数是？
So for now another function is?
丹: 不确定。
&gt;&gt; Dan: Undefined.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们会说未初始化，我被分类了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We will say
uninitialized and I was assorted at all.
我要过来这里，我可能要做我的是我的错
And I'm gonna come over here, I'm probably
have to do my is going to be my bad
笔迹的角度，所以我们会尝试，所以另一个。
handwriting angle so
we'll give it a try, so another.
威尔 · 句子: 逆向重写
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Rewriting in reverse but
另一个函数是调用什么函数的返回值 Tod？
another function will be the return
of calling what function Tod?
托德: 外面 威尔 · 森特斯: 外部
&gt;&gt; Tod: Outer.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Outer
什么我是一个全新的大家？
what I'm a brand new everybody?
每个人: 执行环境。
&gt;&gt; Everyone: Execution context.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 漂亮，就是这样。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful, there it is.
我们忘记把我的新功能从之前的酷属性弹出来了。
We forgot to pop my new function
off the cool stat from earlier.
所以让我们摆脱它，摆脱它。
So let's get rid of,
let's get rid of that.
好了。
There we go.
这就是全球化。
And there it is global.
另一个代码是外部全新的执行上下文。
And another code outer brand
new execution context.
就是这个全新的,
There it is.
Brand new,
我从这个角度这么做很奇怪吗？
is it that weird me doing
it from this angle, right?
或者不，没关系？
Or no, it's okay?
全新的本地记忆。
Brand new local memory.
你会说，是的，看起来很奇怪。
You're like yeah, it looks really weird.
全新的本地记忆，我们保存在里面的第一件东西是什么，伊森？
Brand new local memory, what's the first
thing we save inside of it, Ethan?
我们现在所做的外部调用的内部,
Inside of the call to outer
we're doing right here,
我们保存在本地记忆里的第一样东西是什么？
what's the first thing we save
inside this local memory?
伊森: 柜台？
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Counter?
句子: 设置什么值？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Set to what value?
伊森: 0。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: 0.
威尔 · 森特斯: 然后我们宣布什么，伊森？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And
then we declare what Ethan?
Ethan: 新的函数增量计数。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: New function increment count.
Will Sentance: Yeah new function increment counter.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah new
function increment counter.
就是这样，省省吧。
There it is, save it.
那我们该怎么办呢？
And what do we do with it?
我们不叫它“我们用它做什么” ，伊森？
We don't call it we do what with it,
Ethan?
伊森: 还给我。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Return it.
威尔 · 森特斯: 你认为这里的全局常量是什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Into what global
constant do you think here?
伊森: 另一个功能。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Another function.
进入另一个功能，干得好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Into another function,
well done.
另一种情况，我只是要在这里展示它,
Into another, I'm just gonna show it here,
转换成另一个功能。
into another function.
就是这个。
There it is.
出来就变成了另一个函数。
Out it comes into another function.
进入另一个功能，它来了，但是等等，伙计们，我真的搞砸了。
Into another function, it comes, but
wait, people, I really messed that up.
我忘记做什么了？
What did I forgot to do?
到底发生了什么谁想告诉我到底发生了什么,
What actually happened, who wants
to tell me what actually happened,
当我在第二次运行的 outer 中声明 incrementCounter 时。
when I declared incrementCounter
inside this second running of outer.
当我在内部声明增量计数器时,
When I declared increment counter inside,
如果你想告诉我当时到底发生了什么，请举手。
raise your hand if you wanna tell me
what actually happened at that moment.
Peter 求你了。
Peter, please.
Peter: 你还得到了一个与局部变量环境的关系。
&gt;&gt; Peter: You also got a bond to
the local variable environment.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 这个说法太妙了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That's
fantastically put.
通过什么隐藏的财产？
Through what hidden property?
彼得: 通过望远镜。
&gt;&gt; Peter: Through scope.
是的，通过隐藏范围属性。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
through the hidden scope property.
这意味着当我将该函数返回到另一个函数时,
Meaning when I return that function out
increment counter into another function,
我把所有本地数据都带来了包括什么 Kayla？
I brought with attached all that local
data, which included what, Kayla?
那个当地的背包里有什么？
What's in that local, in that backpack?
柜台。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: Counter.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是字面上的设置是什么？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Is
literally set to what?
凯拉: 0。
&gt;&gt; Kayla: 0.
是字面上存储为0，这就是它。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Is literally
stored as 0, and there it is.
这是附在，威尔 · 森塔斯: 我没有
And that is attached on,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I'm not
我本来想说的，但是我本来想放下的，好吗，就是这样，好吗？
meant to say this, but I meant to
leave it, okay, there it is, okay?
所以现在我要跑了，我要在这里做，伙计们。
So now I'm gonna run,
I'm just gonna do it here, people.
我要走了，我可能没钱了。
I'm gonna run, I am probably out of short.
我打算再经营一家公司，威尔 · 森坦斯: 那也是
I am gonna run anotherfFnction,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That's too
这个角度慢一点，另一个函数两次。
slow with that angle,
anotherFunction twice.
所以这里有个大问题，伙计们。
So here's the big question, folk.
Brayden，我调用过一次我的新函数，我又调用了一次。
Brayden, I've called my new function once,
I've called it again.
然后我拉出另一个函数，再调用一次。
Then I pull another function once,
and I call it again.
Brayden，如果我要控制日志，我在控制台中看到什么值
Brayden, what values do I see in my
console if I were to console log
在这些功能之后的 mechanicus + ，控制台或价值帐户？
inside of these functions after mechanicus
plus, console or the value account?
我的计数器值会是来自这四个函数调用我的新函数
What would my counter values be from those
four function calls two my new function
其中两个还有另一个功能。
and two have another function.
我能看到什么，布雷登？
What would I see, Brayden?
布雷登: 我会走一二，一二。
&gt;&gt; Brayden: I would go one two, one two.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 他说得对吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Is he right?
他说对了。
He's spot on.
为什么是布雷登？
And why is that Brayden?
布雷登: 因为我的新功能背包和美元的背包
&gt;&gt; Brayden: Because the backpack for
my new function and a backpack for
另一个功能是两个不同的背包。
another function are two
different backpacks.
威尔 · 桑塔斯: 完全不同的背包。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Totally
different backpacks.
他们是在一个全新的、完全冷静的执行环境中被创造出来的
They were created in brand new
totally sober execution context for
完全不同的跑道。
totally different runnings for outer.
他说对了。
He’s spot on.
外层是从一个很酷的堆栈里弹出来的。
Outer was popped off a cool stack.
但是当它在那里的时候，它创造了全新的执行环境
But when it was on there, it created
brand new execution context with
一个全新的储存增量计数器功能。
a brand new stored saved
increment counter function.
全新保存的增量计数器功能。
Brand new saved increment
counter function there it is.
我们把它返回到另一个函数中
And we returned that out
into another function and
带来了一个全新的储存国家0商店这个背包。
brought with it a brand new stored
countries 0 store this backpack.
我们不仅得到很少的私人背包数据，而且
We get not only little
private backpacks of data but
每个单独的函数从我们运行的 outer 中得到一个。
each individual function gets
one from our running outer.
非常，非常漂亮的外观划分数据来源。
Very, very nice look
compartmentalised source of data.
让我们做一些其他的调整。
Let's make a couple of other adjustments.
让我们试试这个，如果我要，在增量计数器里面
Let's try this one if I were to,
inside of increment counter
之前我做了柜台加，加上工人声明柜台是0。
before I did counter plus,
plus workers declare counter is 0.
我们的柜台在这里，柜台在这里，柜台在这里。
So our counters here,
counters here, counters here.
如果我有的话，我在控制台上的价值会是多少
What would my, value in the console
told be of counter if I had
我的计数器是零声明每次增量计数器？
my counter is zero declared each
time inside increment counter?
布雷登: 一个一个。
&gt;&gt; Brayden: The one one one one.
威尔 · 森特斯: 一个一个点上，因为那个局部记忆全部
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: One one one spot
on because that local memory all
那是每次都被删除的计数器。
that's counters getting
deleted every time.
我要计算这里的0递增。
I'm going to counter is
zero in here incremented.
把它记录下来然后就没了。
Console.log it, and then it's gone.
再做一次，console.log 它，它就消失了。
Do it again, console.log it,
and it's gone.
没有细节存储在后台。
No niceties stored in the background.
顺便说一下，这只是一个范围规则。
And by the way, that's just a scope rule.
在 JavaScript 中，只要你点击一个标签，一个标识符
As soon as, in JavaScript,
you hit a label, an identifier for
一个非常漂亮的数据，你改变它，你使用它，它就完成了。
a very beautiful data, you change it,
and you use it, and it's done.
你不能再往前走了。
You don't go any further out.
你可以再一次想象一种语言，你可以看到所有的方式，并且
You could again imagine a language
where you looked all the way out, and
把他们都杀了。
hit all of them.
但是这就像我们认为这些事情本质上是正确的时候，范围就不是了。
But that's like scope is not when we
think of these things as inherently true.
它们只是开发者或创造者设计的决策，就像我们一样
They're just designed decisions by
developer or creators like us have
可编程的，疯狂的编程语言，像我们一样的开发者,
programmable, crazy programming languages
who are developers just like us,
和我们一样都是软件工程师。
who are software engineers just like us.
他们选择当你点击计数器的时候，在本地是零
And they choose that when you
hit counter is zero in the local
如果我们在内部声明它。
memory if we had declared it inside of.
增量计数器是零种尽可能的改变它在这里
Increment counter counter is zero kind
of as possible have changed it in here
每次都是全新的。
brand new each time.
那样的话，我们就不能再往外走了。
Well that would not allow
us to go any further out.
如果我们从来没有声明计数器是0里面的外部在所有这样
What if we never declared counter is
0 inside of outer at all such that
返回功能没有在他的背包里。
the returned out function didn't
get counter in his backpack.
但是我们在全局计数器中声明是0。
But instead we declared
in global counter is 0.
彼得，如果我每次控制台登录计数器，我会在控制台上看到什么？
Peter, what would I see in my console if I
were to console log the counter each time?
布雷登: 我需要1,2,3,4。
&gt;&gt; Brayden: I need to 1, 2, 3, 4.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 1,2,3,4，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 1, 2, 3, 4, exactly.
我们一路走到全球，在那里改变它。
We go all the way out to global and
change it there.
正中人心。
Spot on people.
好的，这就是我们的核心原则。
All right, that is our core
principles of closure under the hood.
好了，我们开始吧。
Now, yeah here we go.
个人背包。
Individual backpacks.
如果我们再跑到这里
If we run out here again and
在另一个函数中存储返回的增量计数器函数定义,
store the return the increment counter
function definition in another function,
在另一个功能中，带上全新的储存数据的背包。
in another function, bring with it its
brand new stored backpack of data.
这个新的增量计数器函数是在新的执行上下文中创建的,
This new increment counter function was
created in a new execution context,
因此，全新的独立数据背包。
therefore brand new
independent backpack of data.
然后我们运行另一个函数，我们从它的背包里拿出计数器。
And we run another function, we go and
grab the counter from its backpack.